export const questions = [
  {
    question: "25 / 5 = ",
    answer: "5",
    choices: ["4", "5", "7", "2"],
  },
  {
    question: "57 + 64 = ",
    answer: "111",
    choices: ["111", "121", "102", "101"],
  },
  {
    question: "37 % 4 = ",
    answer: "1",
    choices: ["3", "2", "0", "1"],
  },
  {
    question: "4! = ",
    answer: "24",
    choices: ["24", "32", "16", "8"],
  },
  {
    question: "6 * 12 = ",
    answer: "72",
    choices: ["56", "72", "17", "82"],
  },
  {
    question: "5 * 8 = ",
    answer: "40",
    choices: ["40", "55", "90", "75"],
  },
  {
    question: "138 * 0 = ",
    answer: "0",
    choices: ["138", "1", "0", "-1"],
  },
  {
    question: "0! = ",
    answer: "1",
    choices: ["0", "-0", "1", "-1"],
  },
  {
    question: "12 - 34 = ",
    answer: "-22",
    choices: ["-22", "-15", "-3", "23"],
  },
  {
    question: "43 * 4 = ",
    answer: "172",
    choices: ["305", "502", "172", "94"],
  },
];
